Remember the guy you videotaped
in the alley?
Let's prove your loyalty.
Hello, Ramon?
We need to meet here at...
Ramon!
He has injuries on his body,
so it looks like he was tortured
before he was completely
silenced.
Do you have any idea, Major,
who did this?
Do you know Golda Briones?
Stop investigating.
I posted the video on FlipTok.
What if that syndicate
finds you?
I told you earlier
that you should have told
your father about this.
Where were you between
1 and 2 AM last night,
Major Delgado?
Let's not beat around the bush.
Is he really a hero,
or is he also a member
of the syndicate?
That's the kind of cop
Major Delgado is.
A traitor, a crook,
and an immoral person.
Your father is fooling us.
Bravo.
Your tirades are solid, Andrew.
I'm sure that's trending.
One million views in 4 hours.
Wow.
That's what I like to hear.
Cheers.
So...
this Golda Briones,
you are really taking
her word as gospel?
How sure are you that she's not
an asset to the enemy
or just has a personal vendetta
against the cops?
She gave me more than words,
Yvette.
I have another basis.
What's this?
Bank statement of Major
Miguel Delgado.
This was just sent to the studio
by an anonymous source.
15 million pesos in one year.
His rank is Major.
Fixed salary.
Even a full colonel won't make
that money in ten years.
So, now, tell me.
Where did that come from?
It could be a fabrication,
right?
Photoshop or falsified records,
Honey,
Andrew asked me to verify that.
So you broke protocol?
And you run with the information
on air, Andrew?
Well, the public has the right
to know the truth, Yvette.
You're right, Andrew.
The important thing is,
you hit the snake's head.
It's easier to squeeze it
before he poisons someone else.
Godfather, thank you for coming.
How are you, Joey?
I don't know.
I'm still confused.
But I'm worried more about
mother right now.
Do you think father can really
do that?
You know, my child,
I've been with your father
for a long time.
He's a good person.
Nobody's perfect, Joey.
So sometimes, you can make
mistakes.
What do you mean?
Because once,
Clarissa called me.
Someone called him.
I was the one who answered.
It was a woman's voice.
They said they were meeting
in an apartment.
Come on, Clarissa.
Maybe she was just a coworker.
No!
I have a different feeling.
There's a different...
there's a different tone
in the woman's voice.
So, Diego, help me.
Okay, what kind of help
do you need?
Find out who that number
belongs to, who owns it.
I checked to see who the number
is actually registered to.
Well...
the number is registered
to Golda Briones, my child.
Joey, listen to me.
That doesn't mean your father
is a bad person.
Your father was a good cop...
and he is a good father to you.
But in a situation,
there are times really when...
there are wrong systems.
And if you're not strong,
you'll be carried away.
Godfather.
Let's go.
Let's go inside.
Until now, you've been lying,
Miguel.
It's mother...
Admit it!
When have you been fooling me?
I'm not fooling you!
I was set up!
And what about that girl?
Is that all?
Is it okay for her
to ruin herself
just to make you look bad?
Is that it?
Miguel!
I accepted that you were
always gone.
I convinced myself
it was because of your love
for being a policeman.
- That's exactly what it is!
- No!
You're a liar!
You have a mistress!
That's why you're always gone!
That's why your clothes smell
a different perfume!
That's why someone called you
and wanted to meet
at the apartment!
Because you're fooling us!
- You're fooling us!
- Mother.
You're fooling me!
I'm not doing anything wrong,
my child.
Everything they are accusing me
of is a lie.
He fooled me, Joey.
Your father fooled us.
Mother, maybe we can just listen
to father first.
Are you still defending him?
Even though he is cheating on us
upfront,
will you still take his side?
No, Mother. I just want to hear
father's side.
What side?
What else does he need to do?
All throughout our marriage,
that's what I did.
He can't come home early.
He has a lot of work to finish.
He'll be gone for two days
because he's investigating
something.
All of that, Joey...
I accepted all of that.
All the love, all the support,
all the understanding,
I gave him.
And then, this is what
he does to us?
Was the love I gave him
not enough?
Was everything I did not enough?
What was my fault?
I'll fix it.
Nothing, Mother, nothing.
Buddy,
just let Clarissa think
for a moment...
so that things will be better.
And as for you, don't neglect
yourself either, okay?
Okay.
Father, we'll go ahead.
Do you also believe
their accusations?
I don't want to believe it,
Father, but...
it also made me think
about what the woman said.
The woman you don't know?
Do you believe her more?
You probably can't blame me
either, Father.
But I'm ready to listen
to your explanation.
What? I need to explain myself
just so you'll believe me?
When I got suspended...
and lost my job
because they believed
the accusations against me
that aren't true...
I can accept that.
I don't care what they say.
But when my own family turns
their back on me...
So, they're really separated,
right?
I don't know.
Well, maybe there's still
a chance.
You know, I'm sure your father
will find a way
to make your family complete
again. I'm sure.
I hope so, Peter.
What do you mean?
I know father was hurt too.
I'm sure he thinks mother
and I just abandoned him.
I can't even talk to mother
right now.
You know, this is Andrew's
fault.
He doesn't care about the lives
he's destroying
as long as he can post
a video of himself.
Wait.
The video.
Have you shown your father
the video
of the police officer
who was killed?
Not yet.
I forgot about it because
of what happened.
Besides, it doesn't look like
anyone is following me.
Maybe I'm just assuming
that I'm on the syndicates'
radar.
The videos are really gone,
but only the cameras
in the alley were reset.
The clean-up seems selective.
So that means there's something
they want to hide and erase.
So, it's a clear sign
that someone saw me with Ramon,
and I want to know
who the hell that was.
Matias, you know I can't be
exposed.
But we also saw something.
There's a CCTV that doesn't
belong to the village.
They didn't clean it up.
So it's a she.
What we're looking
for is a woman.
Internal Affairs reviewed
your incident report,
as well as the Regional Command.
What did they say, Chief?
Effective immediately,
you are placed under preventive
suspension.
Pending full investigation.
Dizon's expose didn't help.
There's pressure at the top.
Hot item in the intel
and in the media.
It's dangerous if you stay
in the field.
But I'm not like what they say,
Chief.
And I believe you,
but I'm not your opponent here.
So I advise you,
get good legal counsel,
Major Delgado.
But now, you have to surrender
your badge and service firearm.
Permission to leave, Sir.
Can you still handle it?
Jab, jab!
Jab. Straight. Uppercut,
uppercut. Jab, jab, jab.
Jab, jab.
Straight.
Uppercut.
Ouch, ouch.
- Ouch. That's solid.
- Sorry, Father, sorry.
- Timeout, timeout first.
- It's okay. It's just solid.
You know what...
- You're strong.
- Look.
Hey, you're tiring your daughter
out. That's enough.
What do you mean?
She can handle that.
Right?
By the way, before I forget,
I saw a taekwondo class there
at the plaza.
Maybe you want me to enroll you?
It's only on weekends.
Well, Father,
do I still need that?
Well, you're right here.
You'll protect us.
I won't be here to defend you
forever, right?
There will come a time
when you have to fight
even if you don't want to,
especially if you have
to defend yourself.
Even if it hurts,
even if it's hard,
you have to fight.
Never say die.
- What? Training again!
- Okay!
- What, what? Let's eat first.
- Eat. Eat first.
- It's mommy's turn! Mommy!
- You want to get hurt?
- Hurry!
- No!
That's the kind of cop
Major Delgado is.
A traitor, a liar,
and an immoral person.
This is all your fault,
Andrew Dizon.
Joey, wait! Where are we going?
What's this stuff
we're bringing for?
It's so hot!
You didn't even brief me.
We are just waiting
for DILG Secretary Mendoza
outside his office
on Mabini Street
so we can interview him live
about the case
we are focusing on today.
So don't you dare leave,
Ka-Tiradas.
He's already suspended,
Major Delgado is facing
a lot of civil
and administrative cases.
Well, there's really no place
for people like him
in the police force.
He'll only taint their uniforms,
so he deserves it.
- Hey, hey! Wait a minute!
- Hey, Andrew Dizon.
Excuse me! Who's this?
What? Are you insulting
the police force again?
Are you really not going to stop
with your lies?
Look who decided to crawl out
of my screen.
It's JoeyOnDuty.
What brings you here?
Why didn't you just bash me
online?
I want to do it face-to-face.
Face to face? Why?
Because you know you'll be
embarrassed?
Because you know that everything
I'm exposing is true.
Expose your face!
Rotten and trash, that's what
comes out of your mouth.
Do you know that?
Just like your news,
it's rotten.
So this suits you!
Joey...
- Hey, wait! Joey!
- Oh my God!
What, Buddy?
You're too embarrassed to laugh.
Go ahead, laugh.
Start teasing me.
Tell me your friend is a loser.
That's fine.
It seems you hit something
somehow.
You know, Buddy, I just wanted
to tell you something.
When we were still
at the Academy,
I don't know
if you noticed this.
I was already annoyed with you.
Yes, because I know the time
will come...
when you will surpass me
in everything.
When it comes to firing,
shooting skills, strategy,
and leadership, right?
Yes.
But you know, I have already
prepared for that, Man.
All I did was strategize.
I said I would be close to you.
I will make you my best friend.
So that when the day comes
when we are both in service,
your position will be great.
You will be promoted.
And when you got promoted,
man...
I'd be included too,
I'd benefit.
And it happened, didn't it?
Well, look where my dedication
has taken me.
What's with you, Buddy?
The truth will come out
that you are innocent.
Just keep on fighting, Buddy.
Just remember,
if you need anything...
just say it.
I will do it for you.
Thank you.
That's fine.
What you're doing for my wife
and daughter is enough.
Thank you very much.
That's what you deserve
for all your slander
against Major Delgado!
Sir, I'm sorry.
She went through.
Sir, it's okay.
Why?
What do you know about
that police officer?
And what do you know about
the case he's handling?
I don't know anything
about his case.
But I know my father,
and he would never do the things
you're accusing him of!
Wait...
Major Delgado is your father?
Well, no wonder you're defending
the police so much,
you're biased.
I'm not biased!
You're the one!
It's easy for you to say
that my father is a bad person.
Because you hate the police!
You're the biased one!
The way you act,
you think you're a respectable
reporter, right?
Why don't you prove it?
Instead of all you do is talk
and fool others!
Well, if you think about it,
you don't care about the lives
of the people you're destroying.
You only think about yourself!
Yes,
you're smart,
but that's all you have.
You have the brains,
but you have no heart!
Maybe we can increase
mommy's dosage.
Andrew, no!
Get out of this room
if you don't want to give me
my medicine!
Has Loloy got an update on
what I'm asking him to find?
I told him we should ask
for help.
He said it's not possible
because the police
might kill him.
Is Miguel Delgado the one
he's referring to?
The life of a suspended
officer is pretty good,
isn't it?
Maybe what they're accusing him
of is true.
Just a little patience,
and we'll be able to track down
that woman.
I can't wait to meet her
face-to-face
because she messed
with the wrong person.